// creating an array and passing the number, questions, question and answers

let questions =[
    {
      numb:1,
      question:"Importance of business studies is?",
      answer: "Foundation for higher education",
      options:[
          "Foundation for higher education",
          "Looking for comsignment",
          "Consignee to sign",
          "None of the above"
      ]  
    },
     {
      numb:2,
      question:"A subject which gives insight to business world?",
      answer: "Business Studies",
      options:[
          "Accounting Studies",
          "Business Studies",
          "Computer Studies",
          "Agricultural Studies"
      ]  
    },
     {
      numb:3,
      question:"A room where clerical duties are performed?",
      answer: "Office",
      options:[
          "Office",
          "No such thing",
          "Security post",
          "Plant room"
      ]  
    },
   {
      numb:4,
      question:"What does ATM stands for?",
      answer: "Automated Teller Machine",
      options:[
          "Automated Ticket Machine",
          "Automated Teller Machine",
          "Authorised Teller Machine",
          "Authomated Teller Money"
      ]  
    }, 
     {
      numb:5,
      question:"Which statement is true?",
      answer: "Wages are fixed",
      options:[
          "No  answer",
          "Wages not for casual workers",
          "Wages are fixed",
          "Wages are for permanent workers"
      ]  
    },
     {
      numb:6,
      question:"These are components of business studies?",
      answer: "Accounting, store keeping",
      options:[
          "Extensible Markup Language",
          "Accounting, store keeping",
          "Extra Multi-program Language",
          "Examine Multiple Language"
      ]  
    },
      {
      numb:7,
      question:"_____are documents that flows in and out of the organisation",
      answer: "Office correspondence",
      options:[
          "Office layout",
          "Office equipment",
          "Office correspondence",
          "Closed office"
      ]  
    },
      {
      numb:8,
      question:"One of the function of an office is",
      answer: "Receiving informations",
      options:[
          "Production of intangible goods",
          "Production of tangible goods",
          "Loading and offloading",
          "Receiving informations"
      ]  
    },
        {
      numb:9,
      question:"Selling of goods and services outside ones country is?",
      answer: "International Trade",
      options:[
          "Export",
          "Import",
          "Entreport",
          "International Trade"
      ]  
    },
       {
      numb:10,
      question:"Selling of goods and services within ones country is?",
      answer: "Home Trade",
      options:[
          "Export",
          "Home Trade",
          "Entreport",
          "Loliport"
      ]  
    }
]